goamplify.com 2012-10-14

# FACTS

                                                                                                                        Rev. 11/10
                        WHAT DOES AMPLIFY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
FACTS                   INFORMATION?
Why?                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                        consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we
                        collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand
                        what we do.
What?                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
                        with us. This information can include:
                        - Social Security number and account balances
                        - credit history and income
                        - payment history and transaction history
                        When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this
                        notice.
How?                    All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                        business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’
                        personal information; the reasons Amplify Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you
                        can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                    Does Amplify Federal           Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                  Credit Union share?
For our everyday business purposes –                                           Yes                               No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –                                                   Yes                               No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                             Yes                               No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               No                         We don't share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –                               No                         We don't share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                         We don't share
Questions?              Call toll-free 1-800-237-5087 or go to www.goamplify.com
                                                                                              DTXNU1 (DXPS00 PNDM01)-e

Page 2
What we do
How does Amplify Federal         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
Credit Union protect my          security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
personal information?            safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Amplify Federal         We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Credit Union collect my personal - open an account or apply for a loan
information?                     - give us your income information or apply for financing
                                 - make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                 We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                 affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                 - sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your
                                    creditworthiness
                                 - affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                 - sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                 State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                 nonfinancial companies.
                                 - Amplify Federal Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                 nonfinancial companies.
                                 - Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, government
                                    agencies, plastic card processors (credit/debit/ATM), financial statement
                                    publishers or printers, mortgage companies, mortgage service companies,
                                    consumer reporting agencies, data processors, and check/share draft printers
Joint Marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market
                                 financial products or services to you.
                                 - Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group's MEMBERCONNECT
Other important information
